englishQuestionArray = [
  {
    question: "Which county cricket side is based at Chester-le-Street?",
    answers: ["Warwickshire", "Durham", "Northants", "Leicestershire"],
    correctAnswer: "Durham",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question: "Which monarch was known as the wisest fool in Christendom?",
    answers: ["James I", "Charles I", "Edward I", "Henry I"],
    correctAnswer: "James I",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question: "Which king was married to Eleanor of Aquitaine?",
    answers: ["Henry I", "Henry II", "Richard I", "Henry V"],
    correctAnswer: "Henry II",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question: "Oberon is the satellite of which planet?",
    answers: ["Mercury", "Neptune", "Uranus", "Mars"],
    correctAnswer: "Uranus",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In 1912, former US President Theodore Roosevelt was a candidate for which political party?",
    answers: ["Bull Moose", "Bull Dog", "Bull Elephant", "Bull Frog"],
    correctAnswer: "Bull Moose",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question: "Tomas Masaryk was the first president of which country?",
    answers: ["Czechoslovakia", "Poland", "Hungary", "Yugoslavia"],
    correctAnswer: "Czechoslovakia",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question: "If you planted the seeds of 'Quercus robur', what would grow?",
    answers: ["Trees", "Flowers", "Vegetables", "Grain"],
    correctAnswer: "Trees",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A number one followed by one hundred zeros is known by what name?",
    answers: ["Googol", "Megatron", "Gigabit", "Nanomole"],
    correctAnswer: "Googol",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question: "Which scientific unit is named after an Italian nobleman?",
    answers: ["Pascal", "Ohm", "Volt", "Hertz"],
    correctAnswer: "Volt",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the occupation of the composer Borodin?",
    answers: ["Naval captain", "Chemist", "Lawyer", "Chef"],
    correctAnswer: "Chemist",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a butterfly, not a moth?",
    answers: [
      "Mother Shipton",
      "Red Underwing",
      "Burnished Brass",
      "Speckled Wood",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Speckled Wood",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these is not one of the American Triple Crown horse races?",
    answers: [
      "Arlington Million",
      "Belmont Stakes",
      "Kentucky Derby",
      "Preakness Stakes",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Arlington Million",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Translated from the Latin, what is the motto of the United States?",
    answers: [
      "In God we trust",
      "One out of many",
      "All as one",
      "Striving together",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "One out of many",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first man to travel into space twice?",
    answers: [
      "Vladimir Titov",
      "Michael Collins",
      "Gus Grissom",
      "Yuri Gagarin",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Gus Grissom",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which boxer was famous for striking the gong in the introduction to J. Arthur Rank films?",
    answers: [
      "Bombardier Billy Wells",
      "Freddie Mills",
      "Terry Spinks",
      "Don Cockell",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Bombardier Billy Wells",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these UK prime ministers never served as foreign secretary?",
    answers: [
      "Winston Churchill",
      "Alex Douglas-Home",
      "Anthony Eden",
      "Harold Macmillan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Winston Churchill",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these people was born the same year as Queen Elizabeth II?",
    answers: [
      "Audrey Hepburn",
      "Judy Garland",
      "Julie Andrews",
      "Marilyn Monroe",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Marilyn Monroe",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In the history of motor sport, which of these iconic races was held first?",
    answers: [
      "Le Mans 24 Hours",
      "Monaco Grand Prix",
      "Indy 500",
      "Isle of Man TT",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Isle of Man TT",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In 1718, which pirate died in battle off the coast of what is now North Carolina?",
    answers: [
      "Calico Jack",
      "Blackbeard",
      "Bartholomew Roberts",
      "Captain Kidd",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Blackbeard",
    category: "undefined",
    difficulty: "final",
    moneyLevel: 1_000_000_000,
  },
];
